♪ ♪
♪ I SEE A RED DOOR AND I
WANT IT PAINTED BLACK ♪
♪ NO COLORS ANYMORE I
WANT THEM TO TURN BLACK ♪
♪I SEE THE GIRLS WALK BY DRESSED
IN THEIR SUMMER CLOTHES ♪
♪ I HAVE TO TURN MY HEAD
UNTIL MY DARKNESS GOES ♪
♪ I SEE A LINE OF CARS AND
THEY'RE ALL PAINTED BLACK ♪
♪ WITH FLOWERS AND MY LOVE
BOTH NEVER TO COME BACK ♪
♪ I SEE PEOPLE TURN THEIR
HEADS AND QUICKLY LOOK AWAY ♪
♪ LIKE A NEW BORN BABY IT
JUST HAPPENS EVERY DAY ♪
♪ I LOOK INSIDE MYSELF AND
SEE MY HEART IS BLACK ♪
♪ I SEE MY RED DOOR, I MUST
HAVE IT PAINTED BLACK ♪
♪ MAYBE THEN I'LL FADE AWAY AND
NOT HAVE TO FACE THE FACTS ♪
♪ IT'S NOT EASY FACIN' UP WHEN
YOUR WHOLE WORLD IS BLACK ♪
♪ NO MORE WILL MY GREEN
SEA GO TURN A DEEPER BLUE ♪
♪ I COULD NOT FORESEE THIS
THING HAPPENING TO YOU ♪
♪ IF I LOOK HARD ENOUGH
INTO THE SETTIN' SUN ♪
♪ MY LOVE WILL LAUGH WITH ME
BEFORE THE MORNIN' COMES ♪
♪ I SEE A RED DOOR AND I
WANT IT PAINTED BLACK ♪
♪ NO COLORS ANYMORE I
WANT THEM TO TURN BLACK ♪
♪I SEE THE GIRLS WALK BY DRESSED
IN THEIR SUMMER CLOTHES ♪
♪ I HAVE TO TURN MY HEAD
UNTIL MY DARKNESS GOES ♪
(HUMMING TUNE)
♪ I WANNA SEE YOUR
FACE, PAINTED BLACK ♪
♪ BLACK AS NIGHT,
BLACK AS COAL ♪
♪ I WANNA SEE THE SUN
FLYING HIGH IN THE SKY ♪
♪ I WANNA SEE IT PAINTED,
PAINTED, PAINTED, PAINTED BLACK♪
♪ YEAH ♪
(HUMMING TUNE)
♪ ♪